hopshopgo.com 2019-07-13

# HopShopGo - Privacy Policy | Exclusively for PayPal Customers | Powered by ComGateway

### **Privacy Policy**

_**Updated 25 May 2018**_

#####  **1\. Overview**

In order to operate the HopShopGo service (powered by comGateway) and to reduce the risk of fraud, comGateway must ask you to provide us information about yourself and your credit card that you register with us. This Privacy Policy describes the information comGateway collects and how comGateway uses that information. comGateway takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. comGateway will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. However, as described in more detail in Section 4 below, there are circumstances in which some of your information will be shared with third parties, under strict restrictions, so it is important for you to review this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all services that are hosted on the http:www.hopshopgo.com website and its sub domain, where the services are offered by comGateway. By accepting the Privacy Policy and User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the comGateway User Agreement. Please note that your personal information will be stored and processed on our computers. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used as described in this Privacy Policy, please do not register for the HopShopGo service. 

comGateway reserves the right to amend, vary, delete or add to any of these terms of use from time to time without notice, and the amended terms of use shall apply. This Agreement is effective upon acceptance in registration for new registering Users, and is otherwise effective from November 01, 2004 for all Users.

#####  **2\. Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our service and comGateway asks that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

#####  **3\. Information comGateway Collects**

**Required Information**  
To open a HopShopGo account, User must provide User's name, mobile phone number and e-mail. This required information is necessary for us to carry out our verification procedures, process transactions, issue a new password if User forgets or loses User's password and to contact User should the need arise in administering User's account.

**Transaction Information**  
When User uses HopShopGo to purchase merchandise or services from someone else; comGateway asks User to provide information related to each transaction, including the transaction amount and a brief description of the purchase. comGateway retains this information for each of User's transactions through HopShopGo. comGateway also collects the Internet address (IP address) of the computer or device User uses to access User's HopShopGo account, in order to help detect possible instances of unauthorized transactions. To facilitate customs declarations when HopShopGo couriers User's purchases to User, comGateway will disclose information of User's purchase to the relevant authorities on User's behalf. 

**Additional Verification**  
User's HopShopGo password and mobile phone PIN are to be used when operating User's comGateway service only. User should also not disclose User's HopShopGo password except when operating User's account with HopShopGo. 

**Customer Service Correspondence**  
If you send us correspondence, including e-mails and faxes, we retain such information in the records of your account. We will also retain customer service correspondence and other correspondence from comGateway to you. We retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and violations of our User Agreement. We may, over time, delete these records if permitted by law.

**Questionnaires, Surveys and Profile Data**  
From time to time, comGateway offers optional questionnaires and surveys to our Users for such purposes as collecting demographic information or assessing Users' interests and needs. The use of the information collected will be explained in detail in the survey itself. If comGateway collects personally identifiable information from our Users in these questionnaires and surveys, the Users will be given notice of how the information will be used prior to their participation in the survey or questionnaire.

#####  **4\. Use of Cookies**

Like most websites, our websites use cookies to collect information. Cookies are small data files that are downloaded to your computer or other devices (such as smartphones or tablets) as you browse HopShopGo websites. Cookies may involve the transmission of information from us to you and from you directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Cookies are essential for the effective operation of HopShopGo websites and help you shop and fulfill transactions with us online. They are also used to tailor the products and services offered and advertised to you, both on our websites and elsewhere.

**How do I disable cookies?**  
If you want to disable cookies, you need to change your website browser settings to delete or reject them. Depending on the web browser used, further details on how to disable cookies for the most popular browsers are set out below:

Microsoft Internet Explorer:  
1\. Choose the menu “tools” then “Internet Options”  
2\. Click on the “privacy” tab  
3\. Select the setting the appropriate setting

For Google Chrome:  
1\. Choose Settings> Advanced  
2\. Under "Privacy and security," click “Content settings”.  
3\. Click “Cookies”

For Safari:  
1\. Choose Preferences > Privacy  
2\. Click on “Remove all Website Data”

For Mozilla Firefox:  
1\. Choose the menu “tools” then “Options”  
2\. Click on the icon “privacy”  
3\. Find the menu “cookie” and select the relevant options

For Opera 6.0 and further:  
1\. Choose the menu Files”> “Preferences”  
2\. Privacy

**What happens if I disable cookies?**  
This depends on which cookies you disable, but in general, this will restrict your use of the website and/or delay or affect the way in which it operates. If you only disable third-party cookies, you will not be prevented from making purchases on our sites. If you disable all cookies, you will be unable to complete a transaction on our websites. Finally, you can also delete any cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser.

**The Cookies We Set**  
HopShopGo uses several types of cookies, and each performs different functions.

  * Account related cookies   
If you create an account with us, then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out and select the “Do Not Remember me” option. 
  * Login related cookies   
We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are removed or cleared when you log out. You can continue to access informational pages (e.g. Packages at your U.S. address, tracking your shipments), if you select the “Remember Me” option when you log out. Accessing the transactional pages will require you to log in again. 
  * Order processing related cookies   
This site offers payment facilities, and some cookies are essential to ensure that your transaction is remembered between pages so that we can process them correctly. 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In some cases, HopShopGo also use cookies provided by trusted third parties.

  * This site uses Google Analytics to help us understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track transactions and connections such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.
  * Service provider cookies allow our affiliate partners to provide any bonus that they may offer you for making a purchase or transaction.
  * We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. For these to work, Facebook, Instagram, Google+ and Twitter will set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site, share or contribute content to their site. Each site hold for various purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.

##### **5\. Information Security**

User's credit card and account information are stored in encrypted form on computers that are not connected to the Internet. comGateway restricts access to User's personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to User The security of User's HopShopGo account also relies on User's protection of User's HopShopGo password. User may not share User's HopShopGo password with anyone. comGateway will never ask User to send User's password or other sensitive information to us in an e-mail, though comGateway may ask User to enter this type of information on the HopShopGo website, which will always have a URL beginning with https://www.hopshopgo.com/. The padlock icon found in most browsers will appear locked and the first characters of the website address will change from "http" to "https" if User is accessing a secure server. 

Any e-mail or other communication requesting User's password, asking User to provide sensitive account information via email, or linking to a website with a URL that does not begin with https://www.hopshopgo.com/ should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious and should be reported to comGateway immediately. If User does share HopShopGo password with a third party for any reason, including because the third party has promised to provide you additional services such as account aggregation, the third party will have access to User's account and User's personal information, and User may be responsible for actions taken using User's password. If User believes someone else has obtained access to User's password, please change it immediately by logging in to User's account at [www.comgateway.com](http://www.comgateway.com/) and changing User's Profile settings. 

#####  **6\. Accessing and Changing User's Information**

User can review the personal information User has provided us with and make any desired changes to such information, or to the settings for User's HopShopGo account, at any time by logging in to User's account on the HopShopGo website and changing User's profile including User's password. User can also close User's account through the HopShopGo website. If User closes User's HopShopGo account, comGateway will mark User's account in our database as "Closed," but will keep User's account information in our database. This is necessary in order to deter fraud, by ensuring that persons who try to commit fraud will not be able to avoid detection simply by closing their account and opening a new account. However, if User closes User's account, User's personally identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold or shared with third parties. 

#####  **7\. Contacting Us**

If User has any questions about this privacy statement, comGateway's information practices, or User's dealings with comGateway, User can contact us by writing to us at Attn: Legal Dept. comGateway (S) Pte Ltd, 8 Commonwealth Lane, #04-03 Singapore 149555 or send us an email at [biz@comgateway.com](mailto:biz@comgateway.com)

#####  **IMPORTANT NOTICE**

When using comGateway' s services, you as "User", are agreeing, on your behalf and on behalf of anyone else with an interest in the shipment that the Terms of use shall apply from the time that comGateway accepts the shipment unless otherwise agreed in writing by an authorized officer of comGateway. User's statutory rights and entitlements under any defined service feature (for which additional payment has been made) are not affected.
